you still want more i can respect that let's go gathering cloud sword style now
how did she win 10 against one then again i probably shouldn't be too surprised that girl did kill a spirit
real sister adopted sister does a single word make all the difference in determining the kind
of love one receives what is appropriate and what is forbidden who can say
yeah
What is almost broken by Dal anchor in the world, and you are not one problem
It is still scary
Is a place where the heart drops by the heart
I gotta kiss
All right, please introduce yourself again.
I'm Second Lieutenant Mana Takamiya.
Pleased to fight alongside all of you.
Well, we've got that out of the way now.
Ugh.
Seriously, what's the big idea destroying valuable equipment in a practice match?
Oh, it won't happen again, Captain.
I heard she's the best fighter the Ground Force has got.
Don't let it happen again, okay?
We're about to go over the fight with the Hermit Spirit.
So have a seat and join us.
Yes, of course, ma'am.
The Captain is kind of hard-headed, isn't she?
Being stubborn strategically will play right into the Spirit's hands if she's not more careful.
I agree.
Glad I'm not the only one.
All everyone has been talking about is how you've killed a Spirit before.
Would you mind if I asked you how you did it?
Well, word sure travels fast around here.
Well, no two spirits are alike, so if you want to fight effectively, it's important to remember.
You can't deal with them all the same way.
Hmm.
Yeah, with how hectic things have been lately, I think you'll figure out what I mean soon enough.
That's why I've been assigned here, after all.
Brother?
We got absolutely destroyed in today's match.
Well, that's the life of a backup, I guess.
We might as well get used to it.
Care to explain yourself?
Shido never mentioned he had another little sister.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you a friend of his?
We're not friends.
We're together.
Good morning, everyone.
May I have your attention?
Are you ready for a surprise?
A transfer student is joining our class today.
Didn't Toka transfer a while ago?
Okay, come on in.
Hello, guys.
My name is Kurumi Tokisaki.
Just so you know, I'm actually a spirit.
Um, let's move on.
Well, that's one of the more unique introductions this class has had.
Go ahead and take a seat anywhere.
Before I said, could someone do me a quick favor?
Oh, do you need something?
Since I'm new, I'm afraid I don't know my way around the school that well.
Would anyone be so kind as to show me around?
I'm really sorry to trouble you, but I promise I'll make it worth your while.
Yeah, you betcha I'll do it!
Not you, but thanks.
Oh.
Would you be interested in helping me?
It's Shido, right?
Huh?
Uh, yeah, okay.
So you're completely sure, without a doubt?
I am.
The spirit transferred to the high school.
Well, give her credit for being creative.
She's not your typical spirit.
To start with, she's deadlier than all the others.
Over 10,000 people have died by her hands.
The number's even bigger when you take into account all the spatial quake deaths.
Are you kidding me?
It's been confirmed on our end, too.
I didn't think she'd turn out to be an actual spirit, but this could definitely work in our favor.
So I want you to try and work your charm and make her fall in love with you before the AST attacks.
Hi, Shido.
Are you ready to show me a good time?
Uh, sure.
Which romantic getaway should we head to first?
Uh...
Make your choices quick, team.
He's on the spot.
Huh.
The roof looks awfully popular.
But which of you went with number three?
That was me.
And how did you arrive at that answer?
Through process of elimination.
The school nurse is in her office.
And as for the roof, it's a much lovelier view to witness at sunset.
Just my two cents.
Who knew you were such a romantic?
Hey, Shido, you get all that?
Why don't we start with the cafeteria and student store?
Okay.
What does she think she's trying to pull?
No one else is going to get between Shido and me.
A lot of people like yakisoba.
It's a cafeteria classic.
How interesting.
I'll give you my personal recommendation.
It's this one, the durian bread.
But you'll have to brush your teeth after eating it.
How interesting.
Are you even listening?
Uh, are you okay?
Yeah, just zoned out for a second.
It's hard to concentrate with such a handsome man in front of me.
Excuse me?
It won't do us any good if you fall for her.
Right. Sorry.
She's different from the ones we've faced in the past.
Hopefully Shido can keep his act together and get more info on her for us.
Hm?
Right on cue.
The next set of options.
I say number three.
And why is that?
I'm interested in seeing her panties.
And that's pretty much it.
No, wait!
Have mercy!
Like I'm the only one that thinks these things!
Kurumi, what kind of panties are you wearing?
How did that pervy choice sneak in there?
Hey, question.
Uh, Kurumi?
What kind of panties are you wearing?
Panties?
Like right now?
Numb Skull!
Those weren't your instructions, dummy!
You were supposed to ask her about being a spirit!
Whatever!
Just change the subject or something, moron!
Ease up.
It was an honest mistake.
Would you like to take a peek at them?
Huh?
Yeah.
I don't mind.
As long as it's you.
Stop!
That's good enough.
Thanks.
You're so cute when you're shy.
Moving on.
What did you mean earlier today?
You said you were a spirit.
You don't have to play dumb with me, silly.
Besides, I already know that you know all about the spirits inside and out.
But how do you know so much about me?
That's my little secret.
There's only one thing I can tell you about myself.
Ever since I first found out about you, I've been crazy in love and hoping you'd notice me.
I'm so happy the two of us are finally alone.
It's exactly how I dreamed it would be.
Hey, are you still listening?
Now that I've got your attention, I need you to do a favor for me.
If you think you can handle it, of course.
Toka?
Origami?
This is awkward.
What exactly are the two of you doing barging in on us?
I was just looking for Shido, that's all.
Students are not supposed to hold hands at school.
Let go of him right now.
I'm sorry, but I can't.
I have a crippling case of anemia.
Shido was kind enough to offer his body so that if I faint, I'll simply land in his waiting arms.
My anemia.
I can't believe how pathetic you two are.
Uh-oh, I think my anemone's kicking in too.
Your what?
It makes me sway back and forth until fish are attracted by my cuteness.
She said her anemia, not sea anemone.
Whoa.
Looks like they're fighting over him.
This is intense.
Is he already trying to hook up with a transfer student?
It hasn't even been a day yet.
That's so lame.
Thank you so much for showing me around the school today.
I would have been lost without you, so thank you.
That being said, next time I want to do it with you alone.
All righty then, I guess I'll see you two in class tomorrow.
Maybe it was a good thing Toka and Origami were there.
Otherwise, who knows what would have happened.
Oh, hey.
Where did Origami go?
Oh, beats me.
She probably already went home without us.
Shido, tasty Shido.
Easy, girl.
Don't get excited just yet.
You'll need a little more patience than that.
I'll be sure to save the best for last.
Oh my gosh, I'm sorry.
I guess I didn't see you there.
Yeah.
What was that for, bitch?
You gotta do a lot more for me than just say sorry if you want to go free.
Damn, this one's looking hella fine.
Give us your name before we get down.
Don't worry, we don't bite that hard.
Fellas, hold on a sec.
Oh, wow.
Sorry about the bump.
Maybe I can make it up to you with a different kind of bumping.
Ah, damn, you really are a slut.
Awesome.
We're gonna treat that pretty face real nice.
We're taking turns, and I get to go first.
Come now.
There's plenty to go around.
Follow me and see for yourself how I like to have fun, if you dare.
Why don't you guys hold it while I get this party started?
What the hell?
Help!
Thanks for the snack, boys.
Did I arrive too late?
Well, hello.
You just missed all the fun.
You really ought to learn how to clean up after you eat.
Right, Nightmare?
Burgers!
Tonight I'm in the mood for some burgers.
Ooh, that sounds good.
Go with that!
Hmm, I guess we'll have to see.
I don't believe it.
It's really you.
Origami was telling the truth after all.
Do you know this girl?
No, I don't.
Huh?
Hi.
Eh?
Who's that?
Big brother!
Huh?
This is such a nice place you got here.
I can't wait to see it.
It's nice to meet you.
I never thought my brother would be living with so many women.
Everyone's so pretty, too.
Thanks for keeping an eye on him.
Well, this was unexpected.
How many more sisters do you think Shido's hiding from us?
Who knows?
He's a true man of mystery.
Juicy, juicy!
It's not like I actually knew she even existed.
Wait a minute.
What are Yoshino and Yoshinan doing here, too?
Um, sorry.
Please forgive us.
Oh, no.
It's really not that big a deal to me.
Look at them!
They're so super alike, it's crazy!
That's no surprise.
We are related, after all.
Yeah, it's funny you should mention that.
I've been his little sister for as long as I can remember.
Wow, what a coincidence.
Does that make you my big sister?
No, of course not!
We were both still little kids when my family adopted Shido, so we're as close to siblings
as we can be.
You mean, except for actually being siblings.
Hey, Mana, little sis, I've got a question for you.
Oh?
Go ahead and ask away, then.
Huh.
Well, uh, it's just that...
Well, no offense, but, uh, I don't remember you.
That doesn't surprise me.
It's weird.
The past is such a blank that sometimes I think my memory's been erased.
Huh?
You've gotta be kidding me!
What the heck do you mean your memory's been erased?
I remember the past two or three years okay, but anything before that is a complete blur.
Crazy.
So you don't remember Mom either?
No.
No, I'm afraid I don't.
Then how do you know for sure that you and Shido are actually related to each other?
Is that me?
A lot of little boys look alike.
No, this is definitely Shido.
Like I said, my memory's pretty fuzzy.
But I do remember my older brother going off somewhere.
I was so devastated.
But more than that, I spent every day worrying about him.
That's why I'm so happy.
And now you're sitting right in front of me.
I can't explain.
I'm ecstatic.
Mana!
I love you, brother!
Get away from her!
What do you think you're doing?
What the hell was that for?
Shido is my family.
I'm not going to let you or anyone else take him away from me.
I wasn't planning on doing that.
You weren't?
I just haven't gotten to see him in such a long time.
I'm relieved he's doing well.
And even now, he's still got a cute little sister looking after him.
Oh, thank you.
You should have opened your mouth before I kicked him.
Besides, at the end of the day, there's no beating the real sister.
Funny.
You are joking, right?
Nope.
I'm only stating facts.
There's no bond stronger than blood that I know of.
I think you mean better as a neighbor who is near than a sister far away.
Hmm?
No, no.
An adopted sister's practically a stranger.
A real sister will always be closer because she shares the same blood.
What's the point of emphasizing the blood part?
Adopted or real?
What does all of this mean?
Do you have any idea?
Wake up, you two!
Everyone knows a sister can drive a man wild like Forbidden Fruit, sweet, but just the
right amount of tangy.
Really?
Then sisters drive me wild, too.
I want some Forbidden Fruit.
Quit putting ideas in Atoka's head.
Just how much is your blood worth?
Big whoop.
It's not like a real sister could marry him.
Huh?
Uh.
Um, never mind.
Point is, his only sister is me.
I don't think you make a very good one.
You're not as strong as his real little sister.
That has nothing to do with being a sister, you jerk face.
Hey, girls, let's try to stay calm.
Shito, which do you like more, an actual blood sister or a stupid adopted sister?
Whoa, I'll pass.
Yeah.
I mean, talk about awkward, right?
Um, do you live by yourself nowadays?
Uh.
If someone out there's taking care of you, then I ought to at least meet them and tell them
thanks.
That's not a good idea.
How come?
Is there something wrong with where you're living or what?
I wouldn't say that.
See, the thing is, it's kind of a special dorm for people I sort of work with.
Wait, work with?
Hold on, you already have a job?
Oh, um, I can't really explain it all that well.
See you guys later.
What was that all about?
And Shimada?
Here.
And Suzuki?
And Tokisaki?
Is Tokisaki here?
Tokisaki?
She's gone?
Wow.
I can't believe it.
Just her second day and she's already late.
She's not here.
Kurumi Tokisaki will no longer be attending this school.
I told her to contact us in case something like this ever came up.
Kids these days.
I'm here.
Huh?
Miss Tokisaki, you're very late.
Yeah, sorry about that, Teach.
I felt a little queasy on my way here, so I decided to take a quick nap.
Oh, do you feel better now?
That's good.
Another minute and she'd have been marked absent.
Are you okay, Origami?
Come to the physics preparation room during lunch.
There's something I want to show you.
So, what's up?
Why'd you call me in?
There's a sequel?
Oops.
Sorry about that.
Wrong window.
This is footage from yesterday.
Who's that?
Kurumi and Mana?
Origami and the A.S.T.?
Why?
They wouldn't show up unless there was a spirit around.
No way.
What is this?
The facts.
Yesterday, Kurumi Tokisaki was killed by the A.S.T.
And Mana was the one who took her out.
So you can see, video doesn't lie.
Kurumi Tokisaki should be dead.
But how?
No.
It can't be.
Kurumi came to class.
She's alive.
I know.
Kind of weird, don't you think?
Yes, I do.
I don't have an explanation.
Hello, Origami.
You wanted to see me about something?
Oh, but first, I haven't eaten lunch.
Would you like to grab a bite with me?
You were supposed to have died yesterday.
I was?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, I remember.
You were flitting around with Mana when she murdered me, isn't that right?
What a temper on you.
Try to calm yourself down.
You took real good care of me yesterday.
Cleaned it up as if nothing ever happened.
Well, guess what?
I'm not dead.
What is this?
What are you going to do to me?
Oh, you'll see.
You could say I wanted to try out school, and I even admit it has been a fun experience.
But no, that's not why I'm here.
I'm here for the same reason you are.
It's for Shido.
I think you know him.
You crave him, too, after all.
But unfortunately for you, he means much more to me.
So much more.
So if you know what's good for you, get out of my way and never talk to Shido again.
He is absolutely a delight.
And he makes me feel amazing.
He also looks delicious.
I yearn for little Shido.
I long for that boy.
I want him so badly.
I want his entire body for myself.
I want all the power he has inside.
And I know what it'll take in order to have him.
Before you know it, Shido is going to be mine.
I want him so badly.
I want him so Jaun.
Let's go!